<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Join Scouts on Calder Valley Scouts</title>
    <link>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Join Scouts on Calder Valley Scouts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Beavers</title>
      <link>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/beavers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/beavers/</guid>
      <description>Beavers - 6 to 8 years Try new things. Make new friends. Joining Beavers is just the beginning of your big adventure.
Beavers are young people aged 6 to 8 who:
 Master new skills and try new things Have fun and go on adventures Make friends Are curious about the world around them Help others and make a difference, on their own doorstops and beyond  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Cubs</title>
      <link>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/cubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/cubs/</guid>
      <description>Cubs - 8 to 10½ years </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Explorers</title>
      <link>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/explorers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/explorers/</guid>
      <description>Explorers 14 to 18 years Explorers are for boys and girls from 14 to 18 years old, and meet from 7.30pm to 9.15pm every Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Scouts</title>
      <link>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/scouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/scouts/</guid>
      <description>Scouts 11 to 14 years Scouts are for boys and girls from 11 to 14 years old, and meet from 7.30pm to 9.15pm every Thursday.
Testimonial from Charlotte I enjoy coming to scouts as it is a nice way to get outdoors and do fun activities with professionals. It is also a really great atmosphere as everyone is so inclusive and I would 100% recommend coming to make new friends and memories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteering with Scouts</title>
      <link>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://limograf.com/caldervalleyscouts/join/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>Volunteering with Scouts Each week, we give over 450,000 young people the opportunity to enjoy fun and adventure while developing the skills they need to succeed. We’re talking about teamwork, leadership and resilience – skills that have helped Scouts become everything from teachers and social workers to astronauts and Olympians.
We believe in bringing people together. We celebrate diversity and stand against intolerance, always. We’re part of a worldwide movement, creating stronger communities and inspiring positive futures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>