<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>8th/26th Calder Valley Scouts on Calder Valley Scouts</title>
    <link>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 8th/26th Calder Valley Scouts on Calder Valley Scouts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>About 8th/26th Calder Valley Scouts We meet at Central Methodist Church, Todmorden and have been in existence for over 50 years. We accept all Christian denominations and all religions or none. We do not attend regular church parades at Central, but we do support the RBL’s remembrance day and Veteran’s day parades. We also support Todmorden Gang Show, which has been running nearly as long as the Group!
The boys and girls in the Group do loads of activities around Todmorden and further afield.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description>Contacting Calder Valley Scouts in Todmorden You can contact us:
 by email at dave@caldervalleyscouts.org.uk Or by phone on 08432890163 Or find us on Facebook Or fill in our contact form below:    (function() { var qs,js,q,s,d=document, gi=d.getElementById, ce=d.createElement, gt=d.getElementsByTagName, id=&#34;typef_orm&#34;, b=&#34;https://embed.typeform.com/&#34;; if(!gi.call(d,id)) { js=ce.call(d,&#34;script&#34;); js.id=id; js.src=b+&#34;embed.js&#34;; q=gt.call(d,&#34;script&#34;)[0]; q.parentNode.insertBefore(js,q) } })()  powered by Typeform  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook</title>
      <link>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/facebook/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re on Facebook We mainly hang out on Facebook. Join us there:
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Beavers</title>
      <link>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/join/beavers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/join/beavers/</guid>
      <description>Beavers - 6 to 8 years Try new things. Make new friends. Joining Beavers is just the beginning of your big adventure.
Beavers are young people aged 6 to 8 who:
 Master new skills and try new things Have fun and go on adventures Make friends Are curious about the world around them Help others and make a difference, on their own doorstops and beyond  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Cubs</title>
      <link>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/join/cubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/join/cubs/</guid>
      <description>Cubs - 8 to 11 years Cubs is for boys and girls from 8 to 11 years old who love adventures and the outdoors. They meet from 5.45pm to 7.15pm every Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Explorers</title>
      <link>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/join/explorers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/join/explorers/</guid>
      <description>Explorers 14 to 18 years Explorers are for boys and girls from 14 to 18 years old, and meet from 7.30pm to 9.15pm every Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Scouts</title>
      <link>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/join/scouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/join/scouts/</guid>
      <description>Scouts 11 to 14 years Scouts are for boys and girls from 11 to 14 years old, and meet from 7.30pm to 9.15pm every Thursday.
Testimonial from Charlotte I enjoy coming to scouts as it is a nice way to get outdoors and do fun activities with professionals. It is also a really great atmosphere as everyone is so inclusive and I would 100% recommend coming to make new friends and memories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minibus Bookings</title>
      <link>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/bookings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/bookings/</guid>
      <description>We have 2 minibuses which are available for use by other community groups.
Our newer bus is a 2013 Ford Transit 17 seater. This bus has a towbar fitted so can be used with a trailer. As it is over 3.5 tonnes, drivers need category D1 on their licence to drive this bus.
Our second bus is a 2006 LDV Convoy. It is a 17 seater again, but 12 of the seats are removable and it has a wheelchair lift fitted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteering with Scouts</title>
      <link>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/join/volunteer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caldervalleyscouts.org.uk/join/volunteer/</guid>
      <description>Volunteering with Scouts Each week, nationwide, we give over 450,000 young people (over 100 in Todmorden) the opportunity to enjoy fun and adventure while developing the skills they need to succeed. We’re talking about teamwork, leadership and resilience – skills that have helped Scouts become everything from teachers and social workers to astronauts and Olympians.
We believe in bringing people together. We celebrate diversity and stand against intolerance, always. We’re part of a worldwide movement, creating stronger communities and inspiring positive futures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
